[
  {
    "question": "What does AT-AT stand for?",
    "answer": "All Terain Armored Transport"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does AT-ST stand for?",
    "answer": "All Terain Scout Transport"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does AT-TE stand for?",
    "answer": "All Terain Tactical Enforcer"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where was Han Solo born?",
    "answer": "Corellia"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was Han Solo's love interest on Corellia?",
    "answer": "Qi'ra"
  },
  {
    "question": "Han Solo and Qi'ra worked for what group?",
    "answer": "White worms"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was the leader of the White Worms?",
    "answer": "Lady Proxima"
  },
  {
    "question": "What race was Lady Proxima?",
    "answer": "Grindalid"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Jabba's full name?",
    "answer": "Jabba Desilijic Tiure"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the odds of successfully navigating the asteroid field?",
    "answer": "3720 to 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of Jabba's little sidekick?",
    "answer": "Salacious Crumb"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the singer at Jabba's Palace?",
    "answer": "Sy Snootles"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the Junk Dealer that Rey sells to?",
    "answer": "Unkar Plutt"
  },
  {
    "question": "In episode VII what are Han and Chewie hauling?",
    "answer": "Rathtars"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who gave Finn Luke's old lightsaber",
    "answer": "Maz Kanata"
  },
  {
    "question": "Starkiller destroys what planet?",
    "answer": "Bosnian Prime"
  },
  {
    "question": "What planet was evacuated at the start of episode VIII?",
    "answer": "D'Qar"
  },
  {
    "question": "What language does Chewbacca speak?",
    "answer": "Shriiwook"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Galen Ersoâ€™s nickname for his daughter?",
    "answer": "Stardust"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where did Rey find Luke Skywalker?",
    "answer": "Ahch-To"
  },
  {
    "question": "How old was Padme Amidala when she was elected Queen of Naboo?",
    "answer": "14"
  }
]